Relive your past. Change your future.
A Big Bold Beautiful Journey is a romance, fantasy,
drama film directed by Kogonada.
Sarah and David are single strangers who meet at a mutual friend’s wedding and soon, through a surprising twist of fate, find themselves on a funny, fantastical, sweeping
adventure together where they get to re-live important moments from their respective pasts, illuminating how they got to where they are in the present...
and possibly getting a chance to alter their futures.
David, played by Colin Farrell.
Sarah, played by Margot Robbie.
The Mechanic, played by Kevin Kline.
Female Cashier, played by Phoebe Waller-Bridge.
Sarah's Mother, played by Lily Rabe.
David's Father, played by Hamish Linklater.
A Big Bold Beautiful Journey is a 2025 American romantic fantasy
film directed by Kogonada and written by Seth Reiss.
The film stars Margot Robbie, Colin Farrell, Kevin
Kline, and Phoebe Waller-Bridge.
A Big Bold Beautiful Journey was first released in the Philippines on September 17, 2025, and was
released in the United States by Sony Pictures Releasing on September 19, 2025.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and was a box office bomb,
grossing $20.2 million against a $45 million net budget.
The film explores themes of door, journey, memories.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and mind_bending.